[SHELDON SIGHS]
(Sheldon:)I see no organizational system
in here whatsoever.
(Sheldon:)Which panties do you wear on Mondays?
(Penny:)I don't need panties.
I just need shorts and a shirt.
(Sheldon:)Mother always told me
one should wear clean underpants...
(Sheldon:)-...in case one is in an accident.
-One was already in an accident.
(Sheldon:)Doesn't mean one won't be in another,
especially if I drive.
(Penny:)-Clothes, Sheldon. I need clothes.
-Okay.
(Leonard:)-Here.
-Seriously? Those shorts with that top?
(Sheldon:)All right.
(Raj:)No.
(Penny:)Oh, that's cute.
(Sheldon:)We should have you checked
for a concussion.
Okay, now you gotta help me
put these on.
(Sheldon:)-All right.
-But don't look.
(Sheldon:)-Don't look?
-I don't want you to see me naked.
(Sheldon:)Oh. Well, that's understandable.
(Sheldon:)You may be interested to know
that a prohibition against looking...